

# PHIRIYAKORN MANEEKONGRIT

### WEB DEVELOPER

As a college student with a passion for web development, I seek an internship opportunity to gain practical experience and learn from industry professionals. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript for front-end, node js for back-end, and mongoDB for database.

# EDUCATION

# Bachelor of Science, Major in Software Engineering (INTER)

Chiang Mai University (2021 - now)

### SKILLS

#### Front-end











#### Back-end







# Git & Deployment





### CONTACT

**4** +6695-450-1590

⊠ phiriyakornman@gmail.com

Chiang Mai, Thailand

# **EXPERIENCES**

# **Unarchiver app using JAVA**

Chiang Mai University | 2021 - 2022

 Create a Shopping cart system by implementing all Object-oriented programming in JAVA language.

# **Blog website**

Udemy | 2018 - 2020

 Developed, installed, and configured internal applications, as well as new application releases into test and production environments.

## Food order and delivery system

Chiang Mai University | 2023 - Present

 Developed, installed, and configured internal applications, as well as new application releases into test and production environments.